Diane Wolkstein collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 4: WNYC Stories From Many Lands Radio Show
  - Subseries 2: Audio and Video
    - 102. Africa: New Shoes for Omar, The Storm, afc2016057_dc555; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 103. Africa: Wen'd Yamba Singing Tales of Africa, afc2016057_dc556; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 104. Africa: Namvula, Iyapa and the Water, The Clever T, afc2016057_dc557; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 105. Africa: Sinimore, afc2016057_dc558; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 106. Africa: Out of Africa, afc2016057_dc559; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 107. Africa: Tales of the Basotho by Minnie Postma, afc2016057_dc560; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 108. Africa, West: The King's Drum by Andre Fisher and Harold Courlander, afc2016057_dc561; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 109. Africa, West: Younde One You Don't See Coming, Don't Shake Hands, afc2016057_dc562; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 110. Africa, West: Cameroon Stories, afc2016057_dc563; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 111. Africa, West: The Cowtail Switch, One You Don't See, afc2016057_dc564; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 112. Africa, West: A Story! A Story! The Hat Shaking Dance, afc2016057_dc565; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 113. American Indian: Choctaw and Cheyenne Mythology, afc2016057_dc566; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 115. American Indian (Navajo): Fight Stones, afc2016057_dc567; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 116. American Indian: Saynday's People, afc2016057_dc568; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 117. American Indian: Black Elk Speaks by John Neihardt, afc2016057_dc569; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 118. American Indian: Squirrel's Song, Shingebiss, Sunflower, afc2016057_dc570; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 119. American Indian: The Sound of Flutes, afc2016057_dc571; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 120. American Indian: The Story of Dr. Loon, The Saga of Coyote, afc2016057_dc572; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 121. American Indian: The Magic Wall, Annie and the Old One, afc2016057_dc573; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 122. American Indian (Iroquois): Longhouse Winter by Hettie Jones, afc2016057_dc574; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 123. American Indian (Kwakiuk): The Wisest One, Mink Legend, afc2016057_dc575; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 124. England: The Buried Moon, The Three Heads, afc2016057_dc576; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 125. England: The Cat Who Looked at a King, Mary Poppins Opens a Door, afc2016057_dc577; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 126. England: Dance Mine Own Child, afc2016057_dc578; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 127. England: Humpy Goblin's Kettle, afc2016057_dc579; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 128. England: Jack and the Beanstalk, The Tiny Tiny, afc2016057_dc580; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 129. England: King's Daughter Cries for the Moon, afc2016057_dc685; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 130. England: The Old Woman Who Lived in a Vinegar, afc2016057_dc581; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 131. England: Peter Rabbit, Benjamin Bunny, Flopsy Bunny, afc2016057_dc582; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 132. England: The Stars in the Sky, Catskin, The King of the Cats, afc2016057_dc583; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 133. England: Squirrel Nutkin, The Tale of Mrs. Tiggy, English Country, afc2016057_dc584; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 134. England: The Squirrel Wife, English Country Dancing, afc2016057_dc585; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 135. England: The Tale of Mr. Tod, afc2016057_dc586; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 136. England: The Time Machine, afc2016057_dc587; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 137. England: The Velveteen Rabbit, afc2016057_dc588; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 138. England: Young Kate San, Fairy Ann, afc2016057_dc589; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 139. Arabia: Ali Baba and the 40 Thieves, afc2016057_dc590; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 140. Armenia: Nourie Hadig, The Ashman's Money, afc2016057_dc591; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 141. Burma: 3 Folk Tales, afc2016057_dc592; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 142. Canada: The Golden Phoenix, afc2016057_dc593; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 143. China: A Chinese Fairytale, afc2016057_dc594; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 144. China: Clever-Lazy, afc2016057_dc595; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 145. China: Lord Tang's Dragon Stone from Heaven, afc2016057_dc596; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 146. China: The Magic Drum, afc2016057_dc597; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 147. China: Yin the Wonder Girl, afc2016057_dc598; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 148. Denmark: 5 Peas in a Pod, In the Children's Room, afc2016057_dc599; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 149. Denmark: The Cripple, The Pen and the Inkwell, afc2016057_dc600; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 150. Denmark: The Pen and the Inkwell, The Teapot, afc2016057_dc601; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 151. Denmark: The Teapot, The Last Dream of the Old Oak Tree, afc2016057_dc602; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 152. Ethiopia: The Fire on the Mountain, The Woodcutter, afc2016057_dc603; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 153. German (Grimm): 3 Feathers, Brother and Sister, afc2016057_dc604; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 154. German: The Fisherman and His Wife, Old Rinkrank, afc2016057_dc605; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 155. Haiti: A Piece of Fire, afc2016057_dc606; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 156. Hasidic and Hebrew: Rabbi Nahman, The Emperor's Daughter, afc2016057_dc607; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 157. Hasidic and Hebrew: The Story of Joseph, afc2016057_dc608; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 158. Hasidic and Hebrew: A Tale of Kings II, afc2016057_dc609; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 159. Hasidic and Hebrew: A Tale of Kings III, afc2016057_dc610; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 161. India: Spiritual Stories from India, afc2016057_dc611; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 162. India: The Stone Monkey, afc2016057_dc612; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 163. Inuit: Pitseolak, afc2016057_dc613; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 164. Inuit: The Story of Comock the Eskimo, afc2016057_dc614; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 165. Inuit: Tales from the Igloo, afc2016057_dc615; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 166. Ireland: King Of Toole, Sword of Light, afc2016057_dc616; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 167. Japan: Doll's Day for Yoshiko, afc2016057_dc617; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 168. Japan: Toothpick Fairies, afc2016057_dc618; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 169. Mexico and Latin America: Birds of the Mayas, afc2016057_dc619; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 170. Mexico and Latin America: Lazy Stories, afc2016057_dc620; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 171. Mexico and Latin America: Suni Paz, afc2016057_dc621; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 172. Mystic: Imperial Messages, afc2016057_dc622; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 173. Mystic: The Proud Princess, afc2016057_dc623; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 174. Russia: The Ant from Mishka Pishka Fishka, afc2016057_dc624; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 175. Russia: Anton Antonovich, afc2016057_dc625; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 176. Russia: How Does a Czar Eat Potatoes?, afc2016057_dc626; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 177. Russia: The Lazies, afc2016057_dc627; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 178. Russia: Moolah, The Girl with the Silver Voice, afc2016057_dc628; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 179. Russia: Mourka the Mighty Cat, The Fool, afc2016057_dc629; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 180. Russia: My Mother is the Most Beautiful Woman, afc2016057_dc630; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 181. Russia: The Silver Crest, afc2016057_dc631; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 182. Spain: The Boy and the Whale, afc2016057_dc632; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 183. Spain: The Old Granny, afc2016057_dc633; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 184. Sumer: The Epic of Gilgamesh, afc2016057_dc634; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 185. Sweden: The Princess Who Hid Her Slippers, afc2016057_dc635; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 186. Switzerland: Heidi, afc2016057_dc636; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 187. Tibet: The Rainmaker, afc2016057_dc637; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 188. Trinidad and Tabago: Tall Tales (The Hunter and the Mapepire), afc2016057_dc638; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 189. USA: The Amazing Bone Burglar, Bill, afc2016057_dc639; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 190. USA: Angela and Bear, afc2016057_dc640; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 191. USA: Black Folk Tales, afc2016057_dc641; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 192. USA: B'rer Rabbit, afc2016057_dc642; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 193. USA: The Cicada, The Seed, Everybody Needs a Rock, afc2016057_dc643; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 194. USA: Consider the Lillies of the Field, Three Questions, afc2016057_dc644; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 195. USA: A Mitzvah is a Sanity Special, Dragons Hate to be Discreet, afc2016057_dc645; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 196. USA: Ellen's Lion, afc2016057_dc646; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 197. USA: Family Scrapbook, afc2016057_dc647; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 199. USA: The First Day of School, White Horse, afc2016057_dc648; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 200. USA: Fish for Supper, afc2016057_dc649; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 201. USA: Fly By Night, afc2016057_dc650; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 202. USA: Granpa and Ellen Aroon, afc2016057_dc651; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 203. USA: The Guizer, afc2016057_dc652; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 204. USA: Henrietta, Wild Woman of Borneo,Captain Najork, afc2016057_dc653; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 205. USA: Higgelty Piggelty Pop, afc2016057_dc654; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 206. USA: Hot Balloons, Deep Red Roses, afc2016057_dc655; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 207. USA: How the Old King Gained Wisdom, afc2016057_dc656; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 209. USA: Leese Webster, Spider, Jane on the Move, afc2016057_dc657; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 210. USA: Listener's Choice (Three Billy Goats Gruff, The Backwards Bods, Finnegan), afc2016057_dc658; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 211. USA: A Little Girl Named I, The Elephant and the Butterfly, afc2016057_dc659; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 212. USA: Little Men, afc2016057_dc660; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 213. USA: A Little Schubert, My Name is Aram, afc2016057_dc661; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 214. USA: Me and Neesie, Dinner at Alberta's, afc2016057_dc662; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 215. USA: Minnie Maloney and Macaroni, I'm Not Oscar's Friend Anymore, afc2016057_dc663; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 216. USA: My Name is Aram, The Summer of Beautiful, afc2016057_dc664; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 217. USA: My Noah's Ark, Cloudy with a Chance of Meatballs, afc2016057_dc665; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 218. USA: The Porcelain Man, Oliver Hyde's Dishcloth, afc2016057_dc666; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 219. USA: Rootabaga Stories, afc2016057_dc667; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 221. USA: Smash Small Cars, Elephant and Bad Baby, afc2016057_dc668; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 222. USA: Tell me a Mitzi, The Slightly Irregular Fire Engine, afc2016057_dc669; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 223. USA: Tiffky-Doofky, Caleb and Kate Steig, afc2016057_dc670; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 224. USA: Watson What Did You Bring Me? Which Horse is William?, afc2016057_dc671; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 225. USA: The Way to Start a Day, Hawk, afc2016057_dc672; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 226. USA: What's the Matter with Carruthers?, afc2016057_dc673; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 227. USA: When the Whale Came to My Town, afc2016057_dc674; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 228. USA: Why Worry? Good Old James, afc2016057_dc675; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 229. USA: Wynken, Blynken and Nod, Kisses and Fishes, afc2016057_dc676; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 230. Wales: Prince of Dyfed, afc2016057_dc677; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 231. Wales: Prospect of the Sea, afc2016057_dc678; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 232. Yiddish: Simon Boom Gives a Wedding, The Man Who Made Everyone Late, afc2016057_dc679; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 233. Yiddish: The Fearsome Inn, afc2016057_dc680; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 234. Yiddish: Fools of Chelm, afc2016057_dc681; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 235. Yiddish: Mazel and Schlmazel, afc2016057_dc682; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 236. American Indian (NW Indians): A Book of Indian Tales, afc2016057_dc683; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 240. Birthday for Bird, afc2016057_dc684; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - Haitian Songs and Stories, undated
      - Sound cassette version, AFC 2016/057: SR275; 1 sound cassette
      - Sound cassette version, AFC 2016/057: SR276; 1 sound cassette
    - Magic Orange Trees, undated, AFC 2016/057: SR271; 1 sound cassette
    - Red Lion, undated, AFC 2016/057: SR272; 1 sound cassette
    - Stories from Many Lands, 1970, AFC 2016/057: SR274; 1 sound cassette
    - Stories from Many Lands, April 25, 1977, AFC 2016/057: SR273; 1 sound cassette
- Series 5: Marketing and Publicity
  Publicity materials used by Wolkstein to market her published stories, storytelling performances, and other business ventures.
  - Subseries 1: Manuscripts and Photographic Prints
    - 40 years of storytelling scrapbook, 2007, 1 mixed media scrapbook (Box 21)
    - 40 years of storytelling photographs, undated, afc2016057_dc272; Digital copies of photographs used to create scrapbook; 36 black-and-white and color photographs (PSD, JPG)
    - 8,000 Stones publicity, 1972-1978, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 12/4)
    - Abulafia Dream Songs publicity, 1992-1993, 1 folder of manuscript materials with 1 color photographic print (Box-folder 12/5)
    - Audio cassettes publicity, undated, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 12/6)
    - Awards and certificates, 2000-2011, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 12/7)
    - Banza reviews, 1982, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 12/8)
    - Biographies, 1992-1997, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 12/9)
    - Bouki Dances the Kokioko publicity, 1997-1998, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 12/10)
    - Cassettes reviews, 1982-1999, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 12/11)
    - Celebrating Our Mistakes publicity, 1994-1995, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 12/12)
    - Central Park storytelling publicity, 1970-2007, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 12/13)
    - The Cool Ride in the Sky publicity, 1973-1974, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 18/13)
    - Early performance reviews, 1972-1986, 1 folder of manuscript materials with 3 black-and-white photographic prints (Box-folder 12/14)
    - Eskimo Stories publicity, 1990, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 12/15)
    - Esther's Story publicity, 1989-1992, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 12/16)
    - Exodus publicity, 1999, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 12/17)
    - Fan mail, 1969-1978, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 12/18)
    - Fan mail, 1986-1999, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 13/1)
    - First Love Stories reviews, 1991-1992, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 13/2)
    - French performance reviews, undated, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 13/3)
    - The Glass Mountain publicity, 1999, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 13/4)
    - Haitian News clippings, 1976, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 13/5)
    - Hans Christian Andersen: Classic Stories CD publicity, 2004-2005, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 13/6)
    - Hans Christian Andersen statue 25th anniversary News clippings, 1992, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 18/14)
    - Hans Christian Andersen statue News clippings, 1992-2001, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 13/7)
    - Headshots, circa 1960s-1970s, 6 black-and-white photographic prints (Box-folder 13/8)
    - Headshots, 1981, 2 black-and-white photographic prints and 8 black-and-white contact sheets (Box-folder 13/9)
    - Inanna book reviews and letters, 1982-1983, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 13/10)
    - Inanna DVD publicity, 2002-2004, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 13/11)
    - Inanna interviews, 1988-1990, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 13/12)
    - Inanna performance publicity, 1983-1994, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 13/13)
    - Inanna video, 1989-1990, 1 folder of manuscript materials with 1 black-and-white photographic print (Box-folder 13/14)
    - International News clippings, 1992-2003, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 13/15)
    - Isis and Osiris publicity, undated, 1 folder of manuscript materials with 1 black-and-white photographic print and 2 black-and-white contact sheets (Box-folder 18/15)
    - Jewish press News clippings, 1988-2003, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 13/16)
    - Judith: Woman Warrior publicity, 1989, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 13/17)
    - Lazy Stories publicity, 1975-1977, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 13/18)
    - Letters of recommendation, 1990-1999, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 13/19)
    - Little Mouse's Painting publicity, 1992-2002, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 13/20)
    - The Magic Orange Trees book reviews, 1976-1979, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 14/1)
    - The Magic Orange Trees publicity, undated, 1 folder of manuscript materials with 3 black-and-white photographic prints (Box-folder 14/2)
    - The Magic Wings reviews, 1983-1984, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 14/3)
    - Marketing plans, 2009, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 14/4)
    - The Monkey King publicity, undated, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 14/5)
    - News clippings, 1967-1979, 1991-2005, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 19/1)
    - Newsletters Association Awards submissions, 2001-2002, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 14/6)
    - Ocean Visits Sun and Moon publicity, 2000-2002, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 14/7)
    - Oom Razoom publicity, 1991, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 14/8)
    - Performance recommendations and letters, 1988-1995, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 14/9)
    - Photographs of Diane Wolkstein, circa 1960s-1970s, 12 black-and-white photographic prints (Box-folder 22/1)
    - Press kit, 1993-2003, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 14/10)
    - Psyche and Eros publicity, 1982-1995, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 14/11)
    - Publicity photographs - adult, 1989, 1 folder of manuscript materials with 14 black-and-white photographic prints (Box-folder 14/12)
    - Publicity photographs - "at ease", undated, 4 black-and-white photographic prints (Box-folder 14/13)
    - Publicity photographs - children, circa 1960s, 1 folder of manuscript materials with 9 black-and-white photographic prints (Box-folder 14/14)
    - Publicity photographs -children, circa 1980s-2000s, 8 black-and-white photographic prints and 13 color photographic prints (Box-folder 14/15)
    - Publicity photographs - Hans Christian Andersen statue, circa 1960s-1980s, 1 folder of manuscript materials with 18 black-and-white photographic prints and 17 color photographic prints (Box-folder 14/16)
    - The Red Lion publicity, 1978-1990, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 14/17)
    - Resume and headshots, undated, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 14/18)
    - Romping CD publicity, 2001, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 14/19)
    - Song of Songs performance reviews, 1983-1986, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 14/20)
    - The Story of Joseph publicity, 1992-2000, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 14/21)
    - Storytelling advertisements, undated, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 14/22)
    - Storytelling Magazine - Remembering Diane Wolkstein, 2013, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 14/23)
    - Storytelling posters, 1970-1979, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 19/2)
    - Storytelling posters, 1980-1989, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 15/1)
    - Storytelling posters, 1990-1999, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 15/2)
    - Storytelling posters, 2000-2009, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 15/3)
    - Storytelling posters, undated, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 15/4)
    - Storytelling poster portfolio, 1982-1990, 1 folder of manuscript materials with 1 black-and-white photographic print (Box-folder 19/3)
    - Storytelling scrapbook pages, 1968-1992, 1 folder of manuscript materials with 4 black-and-white photographic prints, and 4 color photographic prints (Box-folder 19/4)
    - Sun Mother Wakes the World publicity, 2004, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 15/5)
    - Tales from the Heart publicity, 1991, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 15/6)
    - Treasures of the Heart publicity, 2001-2003, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 15/7)
    - Tricksters publicity, 1993-1994, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 15/8)
    - Tristan and Iseult publicity, 1987-1989, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 15/9)
    - The White Wave publicity, 1979-1980, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 15/10)
  - Subseries 2: Slides and Negatives
    - Headshots, circa 1960s-1970s, 73 black-and-white negatives (35mm); AFC 2016/057: PH005 (Box 25)
    - Headshots, undated, 4 black-and-white negatives (8x10 in.); AFC 2016/057: PH353 - PH354 (Box 25)
    - Headshots closeups, undated, 24 black-and-white negatives (35mm); AFC 2016/057: PH352 (Box 25)
    - Isis and Osiris publicity, undated, 5 black-and-white negatives (35mm); AFC 2016/057: PH011 (Box 25)
  - Subseries 3: Audio and Video
    - 40 years of storytelling video, 2007, afc2016057_dc305; 9 video files (IFO, VOB, BUP)
    - Ann Izard Storyteller's Choice Award ceremony, December 13, 2006, afc2016057_dc080; Presented to Diane Wolkstein by the Westchester Library Association for her story Treasures of the Heart; 6 video files (IFO, VOB, BUP)
    - Book montage, August 16, 2007, afc2016057_dc267; 7 video files (IFO, VOB, BUP)
    - CBC Midday interview, undated, AFC 2016/057: MV273; 1 videocassette (VHS)
    - Charles Kuralt and CNN, 1992
      - VHS version, AFC 2016/057: MV274; 1 videocassette (VHS)
      - DVD version, afc2016057_dc325; 6 video files (IFO, VOB, BUP)
    - Dance Dolly: Story of a Mother storytelling at Hans Christian Andersen statue, August 15, 2006, AFC 2016/057: MV275; 1 videocassette (VHS)
    - Diane Wolkstein interview on NBC, June 5, 1999, AFC 2016/057: MV276; 1 videocassette (VHS)
    - Diane Wolkstein, CNN, Channel 11, Fox, undated, AFC 2016/057: MV277; 1 videocassette (VHS)
    - Diane Wolkstein promotional video, circa 1970s, afc2016057_dc085; 6 video files (IFO, VOB, BUP)
    - Glass Mountain interview on NBC News, June 5, 1999, afc2016057_dc402; 6 video files (IFO, VOB, BUP)
    - Glass Mountain live interview with Jean Feraca, August 25, 1999, AFC 2016/057: SR277; 1 sound cassette
    - Good Morning Australia, September 2, 1995, AFC 2016/057: MV278; 1 videocassette (VHS)
    - Interview by Canadian radio, undated, AFC 2016/057: SR278; 1 sound tape reel: 5 in.
    - Interview with Diane Wolkstein, May 30, 2003, AFC 2016/057: SR279; 1 sound cassette
    - Interviews with Diane Wolkstein, 1995, AFC 2016/057: SR280; 1 sound cassette
    - Interviews with Diane Wolkstein, Wisconsin Public Radio, December 2003, afc2016057_dc475; 4 sound files (WAV)
    - Interview Inanna, undated, AFC 2016/057: MV279; 1 videocassette (VHS)
    - Jean Feraca with Diane Wolkstein, Wisconsin Public Radio, February 14, 1991, AFC 2016/057: SR281; 1 sound cassette
    - NBC interview about The Glass Mountain and Hans Christian Andersen storytime, June 5, 1999, AFC 2016/057: MV280; 1 videocassette (VHS)
    - NBC News - Storytelling at Hans Christian Andersen statue, undated, AFC 2016/057: MV281; 1 videocassette (VHS)
    - News and Promotional Cuts, undated, AFC 2016/057: MV323; 1 videocassette (Hi8)
    - Quincy, MA - Questions/Answers, May 12, 1989, AFC 2016/057: SR282; 1 sound cassette
    - Roundtable interview, December 19, 2003, AFC 2016/057: SR283; 1 sound cassette
    - A Storyteller's Story discussion event, October 25, 2007, afc2016057_dc289; 8 video files (IFO, VOB, BUP)
    - Storytelling Conversation, December 10, 1991, AFC 2016/057: SR284; 1 sound cassette
    - Tales from the Statue broadcast, 2003, afc2016057_dc047; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - Weekend Edition/Sunday "Diane Wolkstein", June 14, 1992
      - Sound cassette version, AFC 2016/057: SR285; 1 sound cassette